timesalert.com 2019-12-12

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy is furnished with an intent to make our users aware of the usage of information, gathering, and transfer of data provided by the website. Our prime motto is to serve our users and we strictly abide to maintain confidential user data. We have discussed in detail every privacy policy in an attempt to serve our visitors so there might not be any misuse or misinterpretation of information provided on the website. We recommend our users to strictly go through our privacy policy guidelines before visiting the accessing website. The privacy policy is subject to change without any prior information, Stay updated with periodical updates.

 **Log Files and Cookies**

Just like other websites “timesalert.com” also provides information in the form of log files for detailing Internet Protocol address, ISP, Website access information, Number of page views, Entry and Exit pages. timesalert.com relies on cookies to store user information. timesalert.com collects personal information of user whenever they visit our website.

 **Access Control**

If you are a registered user of timesalert.com, we suggest you store authentication credentials in a secure manner. As we are news publishing website you might provide registration number along with other personal information. You can access our website in a secure manner and we commend our users not to disclose information to the third party to receive uninterrupted service from us. If you feel a disappropriated usage of your account without your convention, feel free to get it into our notice.

 **Confidentiality and Security**

If you wish to benefit services from us, one has to register with us with proper information. We maintain your data with utmost confidentiality and we recommend our visitors to provide accurate information. If we receive incorrect information while registering, an account is prone to cancellation without any prior notice.

 **User Submission**

“timesalert.com” is equipped with static and dynamic services as our servers might ask you to upload files. We recommend our users to upload files in the prescribed format and should have content related to the intent with which it was uploaded on the website.

 **Legal Objections**

We strictly abide by the information provided on ‘terms and conditions’ everything featured on the website and our property rights are solely private to us. If anyone sees inappropriate information which is violating any of your copyright rules you can inquire our process. If you have any concerns or issues which are not discussed in terms and conditions, we are eagerly waiting to hear from you and solve them.
